{
    "id": "d7bdc4eb66cd43428fcd0a85ed8a9d3e",
    "title": "Connecting Words Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is neither clever ................................ ambitious.",
            "description": "We use the correlative conjunction neither/nor here. ",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "and",
                "nor"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "............................... being physically challenged, he has great enthusiasm for life.",
            "description": "Despite is a preposition. It is followed by a noun or an ing form. ",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "However",
                "Though"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "..................................... working hard, we could not succeed.",
            "description": "It should be despite or in spite of.",
            "answers": [
                "In spite of",
                "Inspite of",
                "Despite of"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctors tried their best .............................., they could not save her.",
            "description": "However does not connect two clauses. It follows a full stop or a semicolon.",
            "answers": [
                "however",
                "though",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "................................. you start behaving, you will be in trouble.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Unless",
                "If",
                "In case"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The cat must have been somewhere around ................................ I couldn't find her.",
            "description": "But is used to connect two contrasting ideas.",
            "answers": [
                "however",
                "but",
                "despite"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................... he is educated, he lacks common sense.",
            "description": "Though is used to connect two contrasting ideas. Despite is not a conjunction. ",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "As",
                "Despite"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................. you had invested your money in real estate, you would have become richer today.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "If",
                "As",
                "Unless"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I don't know ................................. they will recognize me after all these years.",
            "description": "We can use if or whether to introduce an indirect yes/no question. ",
            "answers": [
                "if",
                "whether",
                "unless",
                "weather"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the town ..................................... he spent his childhood.",
            "description": "Where means in which.",
            "answers": [
                "there",
                "where",
                "which"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "It has been several weeks, ................................. I heard anything from her.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "since",
                "for",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": ".................................. cannot be cured must be endured.",
            "description": "What means that which.",
            "answers": [
                "What",
                "That",
                "Which"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}